威尔 · 森特斯: 同志们，让我们一起走过这个但是
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: People,
let's walk through this but
我已经感觉到这可能使我们的代码更加可重用,
I can already feel that this may be
making our code profoundly more reusable,
想一想，除了倍增 by2之外，还有什么可以传递给它呢？
have a think, whatever else I could
pass to this besides multiplyBy2?
好了，开始了，伙计们。
All right, here we go, people.
1号线，我们在做什么，我的朋友，在这里？
Line 1, what are we doing,
my friend, here?
演讲者2: 我们正在定义函数，copyArrayAndManipulate？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We're defining the function,
copyArrayAndManipulate?
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这是绝对正确的，让我们把它变得美丽
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That's absolutely
correct, let's just get that beautiful so
定义，奇妙的 copyArray 和
definition, fantastic copyArray and
在那里，它被保存在全局内存中。
manipulate, there it is
saved in global memory.
现在注意，当它运行时接受两个输入,
Note now,
takes in two inputs when it gets run,
一个数组和一些实际的代码，是不是很疯狂？
both an array and some actual code,
isn't that crazy?
好吧，下一行，马特，我们接下来节省什么？
All right say, next line Matt,
what are we saving next?
演讲者2: 我们要在全局内存中定义，乘法 by2函数。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We're gonna define in the
global memory, the multiplyBy2 function.
威尔 · 森特斯: 漂亮，就是这个，multplyBy2，小婴儿功能,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful, there it is,
multplyBy2, little baby function,
这时候我要采取希望的数字和
that is when run I'm gonna
take hopefully a number and
把这个数字输出到2我们希望它能这样。
return out that number by 2,
that's what we hope it does.
下一行是伊森的左手边。
Next line over to Ethan left hand side.
伊森: 我们在定义最常见的结果，然后
&gt;&gt; Ethan: We're defining the const result,
which then
调用数组 copyArrayAndManipulate。
calling the array copyArrayAndManipulate.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的，所以我们必须去调用 copyarrayremanage。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, so we've got
to go and call copyArrayManipulate.
希望我们这里有足够的空间，因为这是我写的，亲爱的。
Hopefully we've got enough room here,
because I wrote this in, dear.
第一个输入是数组1,2,3,
CopyArrayManipulate with the first
input being the array 1,2,3,
伊森，你怎么形容我们经过的第二个东西？
and Ethan, how do you describe
the second thing we're passing in there?
伊森: 这是一个被乘法的函数。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: It is the function multiplyBy2.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，这是整个函数的定义,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, it's
the entire function definitionnpeople,
整个过程都是被抓住插进去的。
the whole thing is being grabbed and
inserted in.
所以我们会看到，无论你在哪里看到指令这个词，它都是完整的
So we're gonna see that wherever you see
the word instruction it's gonna be fully
被 multilyby2取代。
replaced by multiplyBy2.
好了，大家，等等，等等。
Okay, so everybody, hold on, hold on.
我知道我们唱了很多我最喜欢的歌,
I know we're doing enough
of my favorite chant,
这是 Stack 的电话,
here's a call Stack,
我们要加入 copyarrayray 和 manipulate,
we're gonna add copyArrayAndManipulate,
就是这样，我们要创造。
there it is to it and we're gonna create.
我会非常高兴，我们要创造一个全新的。
I'm gonna be very happy,
we're gonna create a brand new.
执行上下文。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Execution context.
威尔 · 森特斯: 美丽，那是一种光芒四射的声音，充沛的能量和
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful, that's
a radiant sound, abundant energy and
从你的声音。
sound from your.
好的，让我们创建它，它就在那里。
Alright, let’s create it, there it is.
要运行 copyArrayAndManipulate,
To run copyArrayAndManipulate,
我很难理解垂直的线条
I had very hard time
with vertical lines and
进去，我们走，去哪？
into it, we go, where?
我们的线程会编织进来然后开始运行 copyarrayray 和 manipulate,
Our thread's gonna weave in, and
start running copyArrayAndManipulate,
我忘了什么，丹？
what did I forget, Dan?
伊森: 全球在底部。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Global at the bottom.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 全球在底部，是的，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Global at the bottom,
yep, exactly.
在那里，我们进入它，在我们的本地记忆，看看这支可爱的新钢笔。
There it is, and into it we go, and in our
Local Memory, look at this lovely new pen.
在我们当地的记忆中，第一件事是什么？
In our local memory,
what is the first thing in there?
后面的亚当，我们首先要插入的是什么
Adam at the back, what is the first
thing we're gonna stick in that
操作，执行上下文，本地内存？
copyArrayAndManipulate, execution context,
local memory?
Adam: 数组的参数。
&gt;&gt; Adam: The parameter of array.
威尔 · 桑特斯: 是的，法布有什么指定的论点？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
Fab with what assigned argument?
亚当: 数组1,2,3。
&gt;&gt; Adam: The array 1,2,3.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 美丽而且
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful and
有趣的是，下一个参数是什么？
now the interesting bit,
what's that next parameter?
亚当: 说明？
&gt;&gt; Adam: Instructions?
是的，布置什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes, assign what?
整个函数，multilyby2。
&gt;&gt; Adam: The entire function, multiplyBy2.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 说得很好，但是如果我们不知道它叫什么呢？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Very nicely put, but
what could it be called, if we don't know?
确切地说，没有人知道。
Nobody knows, exactly.
2，整个函数定义,
MultiplyBy2, the entire
function definition,
在那里，它被存放在劳动说明书下。
there it is stored under
the labor instructions.
如果我现在想在这个执行上下文中运行这个 multilyby2函数,
If I now want to run that multiplyBy2
function inside of this execution context,
凯拉，我用什么劳动力来处理多个 by2函数？
Kayla what labor will I use for
the multiplyBy2 function?
威尔 · 森特斯: 指示，她产卵了。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: Instructions
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Instructions, she spawn.
所以我必须在这里写上乘法 by2,
So I would have to write in order
to execute multiplyBy2 inside here,
我会写什么，凯拉？
I will write what, Kayla?
指令然后是素数。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: Instructions and then primes.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太棒了，如果我想提供一个大概的论点
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic,
If I wanna provide presumably an argument
因为它期待一个输入，我把像你知道，像指令。
because it's expecting an input,
I put like you know, be like instruction.
我不想写它，因为我们要做一个完整的暂停和擦拭，但
I don't wanna write it because we got
to do a full pause and wipe down but
我会按照指示做素数会运行多个 by2,
I'm gonna do it instructions,
primes is gonna run multiplyBy2,
输入3会这样运行，这是真正的运行，凯拉。
input 3 is gonna run it like that,
that's really running, Kayla again.
凯拉: 乘法-将句子: 乘法 by2
&gt;&gt; Kayla: MultiplyBy-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: MultiplyBy2
只要输入三个，没错。
with the input of three, exactly.
我犯了一个可怕的错误。
I made a horrible mistake here.
所以如果你在 copyarraymanage 的代码中看到任何指令,
So if you see instructions anywhere
inside the code of copyArrayManipulate,
知道吗，这真的让大家团结在一起，什么？
know that it's really running
everybody together what?
2.
MultiplyBy2.
优秀的美国执行得到了它没有，多倍的 by2，优秀。
Excellent us execution got it for
no, MultiplyBy2, excellent.
好现在我们进入尸体交给马克,
Okay, now let's get into
the body to over to Mark,
标记函数在身体里说的第一件事是什么？
Mark what's the first thing in
the body the function say to do?
标记: 查找输出。
&gt;&gt; Mark: Find output.
是的，然后我们就完成了？
Yeah, and then we'll complete?
Will Sentance: 空数组。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Empty array.
空数组，是的，没错。
Empty array, well yeah, exactly.
好，现在我们开始处理这个函数
Okay, now we're gonna start
working through this function and
我知道我们正在接受这个，也许对某些人来说，这是一个耐心的节奏,
I know we're taking this, maybe for
some people and a patient pace,
但我们要确保这里的一切都安全,
but we wanna really make sure
everything covered here,
以一定的速度在中间，越来越难的东西，我们去。
at a measured pace in the middle to
a more and more hard stuff as we go.
好了，这是输出空数组，数组1,2,3。
All right, there it is output empty array,
array 1,2,3.
让我们进入那四个循环。
Let's get into that four loop.
好了我们进入了四环的主体第一次进入的时候,
All right, we entered the body of the four
loop, the first time we entered it,
丹，我的价值是什么？
Dan, I's value is what?
是的，0，数组位置0是 Dan: 1。
Yeah, 0, array position 0 is
&gt;&gt; Dan: 1.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 1，我们取1，我们要,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 1,
we take the 1, and we're going to,
上面会写什么，是说明书吗？
what it's gonna say, is it instructions?
丹，会怎样？
Dan, is gonna be what?
丹: MultipliedBy2。
&gt;&gt; Dan: MultipliedBy2.
所以我们会有多个 by2输入,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: MultiplyBy2, so
we're gonna have multiplyBy2 input,
0 primes around number multipliedBy2，which was previously.
array position 0 primes around number
multipliedBy2, which was previously.
凯拉又提醒我们了之前？
Kayla remind us again, previously?
说明书。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: Instructions.
威尔 · 句子: 指导，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Instruction, right?
数组位置0的输入，也就是1，我们得到了,
Input of the array position 0 which is 1,
into it we've got,
在我看来，我们要创造一个全新的什么，各位。
that looks to me much like we're gonna
create a brand new what, everybody.
演讲者2: 执行情境。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Execution context.
执行上下文，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution context,
exactly.
这是我们要运行的执行上下文1将被放入,
It's our execution context to run and
that 1 is gonna be thrown into,
1会被放入指令中
the 1 is gonna be thrown
into instructions which
被放入 multilyby2作为输入，让我们看看。
is thrown into multiplyBy2 as the input,
well let's see.
让我们创建一个执行上下文,
Let's create that execution context,
让我们把它放在调用堆栈，威尔森塔斯: 在那里
let's put it on the call Stack,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There it
在调用时，输入是1的多个 by2,
is multiplyBy2 input of
1 on the calls that,
我们走进去，在当地的记忆里，我们有我们的1。
into it we go folk and
in the local memory, we have our 1.
让我们有杰夫，杰夫什么是我们的参数名称
Let's have Jeff,
Jeff what is our parameter name for
这个标签的值是1？
that label for that value 1?
杰夫: 输入。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Input.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 他是对的，这是输入参数，这就是它。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: He is right,
it's the input parameter and there it is.
然后我们输入2,1乘以2，我们得到2，我们返回它然后
We then do input by 2, 1 by 2,
we get 2, we return it out and
看看这些家伙，指令是多个 by2,
look at that folks,
instructions which is, multiplyBy2,
输入的1乘以输入的1是字面上要评价。
input of 1 multiply by input of 1
is literally going to evaluate.
所以会变成2的输出,
So is gonna become the output of 2,
这是2的结果，凯拉，我们怎么处理这个2？
there it is an outcomes of 2 and
Kayla what do we do with that 2?
我们已经把它放到输出数组中了。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: We've pushed it
into the output array.
Will Sentance: 我们将它推入输出数组。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We push
it into the output array.
有人，进入输出数组，然后
There is people,
into the output array it goes and
死刑会导致什么后果 Kayla？
there's execution causes
what happens with it, Kayla?
它消失了。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: It goes away.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们把它从调用堆栈上取下来，它就消失了,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We pop it off
the call Stack, it goes away,
也引导你除了返回值。
also lead you besides
the returned out value.
完美我们从 Stack 那里得到的更有活力的清除,
Perfect we get it off the call Stack,
more energetic erasing,
这不是有点粗暴，不是坏在所有。
there is this is not as kinda
roughing not bad at all.
现在我们点击数组，进入四个循环，再来一次，这次,
Now we hit the array, into the four
loop we go again and this time,
我的价值 Brayden 是什么？
i's value, Brayden, is what?
布雷顿: 1 威尔 · 森塔斯: 是1,
&gt;&gt; Braydon: 1.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's 1,
位置1的数组是2号。
array at position 1 is number 2.
我们用那2号球，布雷登，然后我们把它塞进什么，布雷登？
We take that 2, Brayden, and
we stick it into what, Brayden?
布雷顿: 说明。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: Instructions.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 哪一个是真的？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Which is really?
2.
&gt;&gt; Braydon: multiplyBy2.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太棒了，它有多个 by2。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic,
it's multiplyBy2.
然后哪个会回来，哪个会进去，哪个会出来，布拉登？
Which will then return out,
in goes the 2, what returns out, Braden?
布雷顿: 4 威尔 · 森塔斯: 4，没错,
&gt;&gt; Braydon: 4.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 4, exactly,
创建执行上下文，将其放到调用堆栈上。
the execution context is created,
put it on the call stack.
好了，我们开始吧-演讲者2: [笑]
Okay, we do it-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
威尔 · 森塔斯: 就在那儿，在电话里
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There it is on the call
堆栈，这是它的2，所以我只是画它,
stack, there it is with the 2,
so I'll just draw it,
结果4它会被存储在哪里，布莱登？
outcomes 4 and
it's gonna be stored where, Braden?
Braydon: 推入输出数组
&gt;&gt; Braydon: Pushed on
into the output array
推入输出
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Pushed into the output
数组。
array.
2里面的标签是什么，布拉登？
The label for
2 inside multiplyBy2 was what, Braden?
讲者二: 输入法 威尔 · 斯坦斯: 输入,
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Input.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Input,
这就是参数名，没错，一点没错，我得到了6，有2,4,6，很好。
that was the parameter name, exactly, spot
on, I got 6, there is 2, 4, 6, excellent.
现在，伊森，我们完成了四个循环，我们最后要做什么？
And now Ethan, we finished our four loop,
we're gonna do what finally?
伊森: 我们要返回输出值。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: We're gonna
return the value of output.
Will Sentance: Beautiful，返回输出值，数组，2,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful,
return the value of output, the array, 2,
4,6，到结果，就是这个数组2,4,6。
4, 6, into results,
there it is, the array 2, 4, 6.
很好，我们已经构建了一个函数，看看这个，我们不需要这样做
Fork wonderful, we've built out a function
that, look at this we didn't have to
以任何方式预先确定我们要对数组的每个元素做什么。
in any way predetermine what we're
gonna do to each element of the array.
我们把它留给了机构，并且
We left it blank with institutions, and
就像我们让我们的地方，把我们的参数安排在最佳位置一样。
just like we had our place order
our parameter in our best position.
它是否有一个占位符参数用于传递数组1,2,3，它可以
Does it have a placeholder parameter for
passing in that array 1,2,3, which could
是1,2,3,4,5,6，可能是7,8,9，可能是其他的。
have been 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, could have
been 7, 8, 9, could have been whatever.
所以2，我们留了一个占位符，表示我们要对数组中的每个元素做什么,
So 2, we left a placeholder for what we're
gonna do to each element of that array,
一个小空白，我们填写了一个函数，接受了一个输入,
a little blank, and we filled it in
with a function that took in one input,
我们已经准备好了，我们使用了它，我们接受了输入,
we were ready for it,
we used it, we took that input,
我们将结果返回，并将其输出。
we returned out the result and
we pushed it into output.
因为我们已经复制了一个操作函数
For we've made our copy
of a manipulate function
通用可重用，我们现在可以编辑它的代码，因为我们
general reusable,
we can now edit its code because we
留下了一些空白，我们可以稍后再填写，你不能编辑函数。
left a little blank bit that we can fill
in later on, you can't edit functions.
但是如果你为他们的代码留下一点空间一点占位符,
But if you leave a little space, a little
placeholder for some of their code,
你可以编辑函数，保存一次，然后反复使用。
you can edit functions, save them once,
use it again and again.